[BILLY] I don't want
our efforts to go to waste.
Mission accomplished, dude.
I got his location!
[BILLY] I'm outside the troll's house.
[JORDAN] That's dangerous!
[CALOY] Who's there?
- [CALOY] Hey!
- [BILLY] Who's giving you those orders?
[CALOY] Why would I tell you?
Ms. Cariño.
Help!
- [BREATHING HEAVILY]
- [CALOY] Who are you?!
[GRUNTS]
- [GROANS]
- [KNIFE SWISHES]
- [BILLY] Auntie Pres?
- [PRECIOUS] Oh, Billy?
[PRECIOUS] We have a visitor.
- Ms. Billy!
- [BILLY] Abi!
I wanted to thank you
because our conversation
really helped me a lot.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
JESSIE: YOU'RE TRENDING!
COLLAB SOON
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[LINE RINGING]
Hello?
Do something.
If not, you'll get dragged into this.
I don't want to go to jail again.
I've been here numerous times.
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
Your temperature's very high.
You okay?
I am completely fine.
Stop saying you're okay. You're not okay.
Okay.
Time to drink. Sorry, sit up.
One, two, three, okay.
- [GRUNTS]
- Sorry.
Here. Give me your hand.
["KULIMLIM" BY ANGELA KEN PLAYING]
Okay.
If you're still not feeling well tomorrow,
I'll take you to the hospital, okay?
[JORDAN EXHALES]
- All right.
- Okay.
[SETS CUPS DOWN]
Move a bit, sorry.
[JORDAN HUMS]
["KULIMLIM" CONTINUES]
[SOFT GRUNT]
- Good morning, Billy!
- Good morning, naughty boy.
[BILLY GROANS]
- Billy. Why'd you sleep here?
- Hm?
I wonder why.
Just because. I just missed you.
Am I not allowed in here anymore?
- You're still allowed!
- I'm still allowed? Okay.
[BILLY GROANS]
I saw this last night. What's this?
I want to fix my school grades.
I heard it's hard
to get into those schools.
- College universities?
- Yes.
But it's still too early for this.
What do they say is the best school?
It's there in California!
The University of Kingsley.
That's the best school
for software engineering!
- Hmm!
- But…
It's too expensive.
I could study here too.
There are also many Philippine schools
that offer software engineering.
I have my top three schools I can go to.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
University of Kingsley.
Noted. Okay, you'll study here.
- Really, Billy?
- Mm-hmm!
- Sure?
- Promise?
- Promise.
I'm going to study well,
so your efforts won't go to waste.
When I graduate,
you can stop working,
so you can finally rest.
You know I'd do anything for you, right?
That's okay. I love you.
I love you, Billy.
Thank you for everything.
[GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Are our quick response templates
for LoveLine ready?
- Yes, chief.
- Okay, good.
Please remind the Ads Team
that we have to be ready
by next week for the push campaign.
- [BLAIRE] Okay.
- Thank you.
- How's Jordan?
- Is he still alive?
Calm down. He's fine now.
- Ahh…
- [MARJ] That's good.
I plan to vlog
about everything that happened.
Let's repost it,
so we can push the fact that
you're the real victim.
Speaking of pushing…
The equipment's getting delivered.
They're already charging me
for the remaining balance of our payment.
Will we still push through with it?
I mean, the price of the equipment,
the additional manpower, the new gadgets,
and the software is no joke.
My crystals can't take this anymore.
Ralph's friends with the supplier.
Maybe he can discuss a refund.
No. I'll finance this.
This can't not push through just because--
Of her.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Billy, can we talk?
I hate to admit this, but…
I realized that I'm acting pathetic.
I mean,
with my beauty,
I'm acting crazy running after a guy
that doesn't even like me.
So what are you doing here?
Are you here
because you're feeling guilty?
Are you confessing
that you ordered Carlos Toledo
to destroy my company?
You're acting guilty now
because Jordan got involved.
Is that it?
[VALERIE SIGHS]
Billy.
I may be desperate to win Jordan back,
but you know me.
I can destroy someone
if I want to destroy them.
But I won't go as low and as far
as working with criminals.
And spray paint a car?
Do you really think I would do that?
[VALERIE SIGHS]
I'm here because I wanna help you guys.
And I wanna make it up to Jordan.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Guys, let's be real.
We all know that fake news is everywhere.
And, sadly,
recently, Ms. Billy Cariño, LoveList CEO,
has fallen victim to one.
Someone's trying to destroy her company,
and we're not buying it.
You guys might be wondering,
"Why are you on her side?
Don't you have beef with each other?"
Well, yeah, but that's a different story.
With this topic, I want you to hear it
straight from the source.
Here to spill, Ms. Billy Cariño.
Thank you.
This isn't just an ordinary issue.
This is a crime.
I don't know who they are,
what it was for,
or why they even went so far
as to hire a hacker troll.
But the good news is,
that hacker is now in jail.
And when we found them, they said
that they don't know
who commissioned them.
They were just paid to do it.
People might think that this is
just a petty cyberwar.
But this is a serious matter to us.
I think everyone knows
what happened to my friend,
the Tech Lead of LoveList,
Jordan Valentin.
Jordan is okay now.
But what we're not okay with
is how we still can't track down
the mastermind behind this.
The reason I'm here right now
is because we need your help.
If you know anything
or if you have any kind of information
that can help with our case,
please, don't hesitate to reach out.
[BILLY] Moving forward,
I just want to let you all know
that this setback won't stop LoveList.
At the end of the day,
the responsibilities of LoveList
are conveyed clearly to its users.
[BILLY] And with that,
we will push through with
our plans for LoveList,
and that includes LoveLine.
Because I believe that the truth
always has its way
of revealing itself.
And love?
Love always wins.
So whoever you are
who's trying to mess with us,
no matter where you are,
I'll find you.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[TENSE MUSIC FADES]
Gosh, my followers will love this!
Hey, guys! Right now, we're in Ja--
Hi! Hi, guys!
Uh, isn't this my content?
This isn't supposed to be for you to post!
[NERVOUS CHUCKLE] This is an exclusive!
Just kidding! She's getting pissed.
You're getting pissed!
It won't be an exclusive anymore.
My fans might get sick of it.
They're so over our drama.
All right, go ahead. Continue. [GIGGLES]
Okay… let's go over there!
Wait, this one's exclusive.
Exclusively mine. [GIGGLES]
- I'm all yours, baby.
- Aw!
Wow! How sweet!
Let's move on to these two!
[BOTH CLEARING THROATS]
Of course, he's all mine too! [GIGGLING]
Of course!
- Hi!
Hey, what the?!
Oh, no, I was just stretching my neck…
- Do you know her?
- Oh, no…
Hey, bro!
[NERVOUS CHUCKLE] Hey!
- Let's go, Toni. [CHUCKLING]
- She's not even that pretty.
By the way, Marj, have you
already chosen someone?
- You have two matches, right?
- Hmm… [CLICKS TONGUE]
The right one at the right time,
as they say, right?
I agree. Love at the right time!
- Mm-hmm.
- Mm-hmm!
- Okay! Bye, guys!
- Bye!
[MARJ GIGGLING]
That's right. Love at the right time!
Drinks! Drinks for everyone!
Wow, you're acting as if
you're in a relationship!
Well, I did say
love at the right time, didn't I?
He's right.
You know what, I agree.
Love at the right time.
And guess what?
I think it's almost time.
- Okay!
- [LAUGHTER]
- We'll just make our rounds.
- Sure!
[DIGITAL TRILLING]
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
Billy, thank you so much for accepting me
to be a part of the LoveList family.
I'm so excited to be
your honorary consultant.
[LAUGHS]
Anyways,
I think that me and Marj
will have a good working chemistry.
I hope she learns a lot from me.
[LAUGHS]
Cheers!
- Cheers!
- [BOTTLES CLINKING]
Welcome to the LoveList family, Val.
- Cheers?
- [VALERIE] Cheers.
[BILLY GIGGLES]
[THUDS]
I'll just go to the restroom.
Mmm. Take a seat.
I'll just sit for a bit.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[THUDDING]
I thought you were going to the restroom?
Girl… what is it?
What do you mean?
I can sense it.
Just spill it.
Okay, fine.
- I'll be honest, okay?
- Mm-hmm.
If it's just damage control,
I can do it too.
The interview
that Valerie did on her vlog?
I can do that!
Do you have five million subscribers?
Exactly.
Marj, you cannot argue with success, okay?
Just look at the impact of Val's vlog.
LoveList's membership shot back up again.
It's that easy?
Just because of that,
she gets to be a part of us?
She's a content creator now too?
Wow!
Does our chief really believe
that she's innocent?
Next time, if you have questions,
go to me directly.
It's better for me if we communicate more.
Sorry, chief.
It's just that…
things are happening way too fast.
Like, honestly, I can't keep up.
Like how…
how sure are we that Valerie
has nothing to do
with the sabotage?
I am for peace, Marj.
Didn't Valerie tell us that
she's got nothing to do with it?
Then I want to give her
the benefit of the doubt.
Now, I won't say
she completely has my trust.
She still has to work for it.
We're on the same page, okay?
So, trust me, relax,
and let's enjoy the night.
- Cheers?
- Cheers!
- [GIGGLING] Cheers!
- [TONI GIGGLING] Just chill.
- Sorry. [GIGGLING]
Val!
Hey, thanks for helping us at the company.
Thank you too.
I know you're the reason
why Billy accepted me
into your team.
I just wanted to clear the air between us.
You know,
we go way back after all.
Hey, don't get any ideas.
As much as I want to say that
I'm doing this for you,
that's really not the case.
The truth is,
I'm doing this for myself.
For my peace of mind.
Okay.
Good.
- [DIGITAL TRILLING]
- [FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
- Auntie Pres!
- Whoa! Hey!
- Oh my gosh!
- Hey, give it back!
- Oh, thank you, Lord!
- What're you thanking Him for?
- What're you on?
- Auntie Pres!
Is this a blessing or what?
Wait a minute, hold it.
Let me make it clear.
- I only downloaded this…
- Mm-hmm?
…because… uh,
you guys need extra members.
- I just helped out. Charity!
- Okay!
You're really going to lie to me?
I monitor all of the sign-ups.
- Hmm.
- Hmm?
Give it to me. Let me see.
Just let me take a peek.
Brandon!
Wow! It's a 97% match!
This is really high, Auntie.
Ooh…
- How about it? Want to give it a try?
- Huh?
- Go for it. Accept it.
- Here. Press it.
- I might press it by accident!
- Just accept it!
- No, I won't accept it!
- You-- I'm not sure about this.
- You don't want to?
No, I--
Okay.
I'm not sure if I'm ready yet
because maybe I still haven't
moved on from my husband,
so, no.
- Let's leave it at that.
- Uh-huh…
- Let's leave it.
- There's only one way to find out!
- [PRECIOUS FAKE SOBBING]
- Uncle Rico is already smiling
down from heaven.
It's been a few years since then too.
- Okay, uh…
- Mm-hmm.
Billy, let me just tell you that Rico
had a heart attack on the very day
of our wedding, okay?
I'm scared that it'll happen again!
- I don't want that.
- It won't happen again.
God is gracious.
He'll give you a second, third,
and even fourth chance.
- And now, it's your chance!
- [SHRIEKS]
- No! No!
- Come on!
But, wait, what do you--?
Why is it my chance?
- What do you mean?
- Why don't you give yourself a chance?
Why me and not you?
Oh, no, chances come by,
and mine hasn't arrived yet.
- But yours is already here.
- Oh, really? [LAUGHING]
- It's one click away!
- [LAUGHING] No!
No, no, no!
Honey, there's no chance anyone's coming.
Besides, it's already 10:00 p.m.
- [YAWNS] Oh, I'm getting sleepy!
- You're getting sleepy?
- Let's go to bed.
- Come on.
BecauseLoveLine launches tomorrow.
- Tomorrow!
- I'll be there, yes.
Don't cook. Let's eat out afterward.
Huh? That's a brilliant idea!
That's the only brilliant idea
you've had tonight!
- Well done!
- Oh! Good night!
- Let's go to bed! [SCREAMS]
- Good night!
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DOOR CREAKS]
[MUSIC STOPS ABRUPTLY]
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
Dude?
Everything okay?
Yeah. I've checked
the user interface flow.
There was just a minor bug,
but I already fixed it.
- Okay.
- It's running lag-free.
- We're good to go.
- You sure?
Yeah.
By the way,
I followed up with the police
the other day.
Mm-hmm?
Unfortunately,
the CCTV cameras around
Caloy's area weren't working,
and they couldn't trace
the number that contacted him.
Sorry, dude.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
I've already invested
a lot of money into this, dude.
Are you worried?
That LoveLinemight become a target
once it takes off?
What do you mean, "once it takes off?"
I just know LoveLine will work.
We just have to be more prepared
and more careful.
It's nothing.
I'm fine. Don't blame yourself, dude.
Auntie, Oli, say hi to the vlog first!
- Hello!
- Hi!
We'll head over there first, okay?
- Sure, Auntie.
- Bye!
- See you.
So here it is,
the biggest plot twist of LoveList.
LoveLine!
A helpline for the brokenhearted.
It's our in-app dating coach
and support feature.
At LoveList, we believe that
no woman should ever
have to go through heartbreak alone.
This is your venting-out corner.
A safe space for everyone.
If you're looking for free therapy,
this is it.
Right, chief?
[BILLY] Yes. Hold on.
This is a space where you can reach out,
be helped, be heard.
When it hurts, this is where you come.
[PHONE RINGING]
Hi. Thank you for calling LoveLine,
your safe space for honest
and heart-to-heart conversation.
How can I support you today?
I'm a widow.
I met John on LoveList.
[WOMAN] He's so sweet and caring.
The problem is,
he lost his job.
Should I lend him money?
Noreen, not yet.
Especially if your relationship
is still new
and he's already asking for money.
See first if he's still sincere
even when you can't give him anything.
His reaction will be very telling.
So be discerning, okay?
Mm-hmm.
Thank you.
- Okay, good job.
- Chief!
Yes?
This caller seems to know you.
Me?
Hello?
Hi, this is Billy speaking.
How can I support you today?
Oh my gosh, Ms. Billy!
Is that really you?
I'm so sorry!
When someone answered earlier,
I thought it was you,
so I said, "Ms. Billy,"
but it turned out
it was one of your agents.
Then they suddenly called you.
I'm so sorry.
Am I bothering you, Ms. Billy?
Abi, it's you.
Um…
Not at all.
[ABI] I just wanted to congratulate you.
Congratulations!
I just wanted to make sure this was real.
I thought maybe I'd be talking to a bot,
but it turns out
it's a real person answering.
That's amazing. Congratulations!
A bot?
How'd you know about that?
Well, Ms. Billy, we own an internet café.
So I know a little about those things.
We also have a repair shop.
You know, for fixing gadgets and stuff.
Oh, okay.
Abi, thanks for your support,
but I have to end the call now.
We've got a lot of callers today.
If you ever have time,
just drop by the office.
[SQUEALS] Really?
Okay, Ms. Billy!
I'll definitely look forward to it.
Congratulations again!
You're amazing, idol!
Okay. Thank you, Abi. Bye!
Okay.
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DOOR CREAKS]
[SQUEALING]
This room is so beautiful!
This bed is gorgeous!
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GROANS]
It's so soft!
This feels amazing!
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
Must be nice.
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
I feel a sense of…
Potential? Connection?
Auntie, have you seen
my red shoes?
[PRECIOUS] First,
you lost your keys.
Now, it's your shoes.
Someone's looking
for you downstairs.
But she doesn't have
an appointment.
Do you think I could be
part of LoveList?
Who bailed you out?
How many times
do I have to tell you both?
I don't even know
who my boss is!
If you say anything to that man,
I'll finish you off!
- Caloy!
- And your family--
[BLOWS LANDING]
Who's your boss?
I'd never put you in danger.
- Hello?
- Benilda?
Sweetie?
[PRECIOUS] Billy, why do you think
he suddenly called you?
Let's check out the people
boxing over there.
[JORDAN] I'll teach you.